

# Stefan Ciobanu, Javascript Developer/React JS

CLUJ-NAPOCA, 400268, ROMANIA -- stefan.e.ciobanu@gmail.com

DETAILS

Oasului, 86-90

Cluj-Napoca, 400268

Romania

+40751632715

DATE OF BIRTH

23.10.1990

NATIONALITY

Romanian

DRIVING LICENSE

В

# PROFILE

Operating in the entrepreneurial world, working closely to IT companies for more than 4 years, I started to grow more and more my interest for technology. My technical skills were strongly developed during my attendance at the course from the Informal School of IT. I learned to work with coding languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React JS. Furthermore, working as a Wordpress developer helped me grow my technical expertise with creating websites and optimising them from the SEO perspective. Overall, I am a quick learner and an easy adaptable person.

#### **EXPERIENCE HISTORY**

#### Javascript Developer, Informal School of IT

Sep 2020 — Present, Cluj-Napoca

I had opportunity to work and operate with:

• JavaScript

• React

• Node

Bootstrap

# Wordpress Developer, Thrupny

Aug 2019 — Present, CLUJ-NAPOCA

• Developing website on Wordpress

· Optimizing the site

• SEO

• Security

· Speed optimization

• Quality Assurance

https://www.thrupny.com/

# Wordpress Developer, Apex Privacy Podcast

Dec 2020 — Dec 2020

• WordPress site development

• Security

• SEO

• Administration

# Co-Founder , Sesabro Company SRL

Aug 2016 — Apr 2020, CLUJ-NAPOCA

https://fruitsdelivery.ro/

LINKS

Linkedin

**SKILLS** 

Leadership Skills

Accounting

WP development

SEO

Creative Problem Solving

Customer and Personal

Service

Administrative Skills

Creative Thinking

Hard Working

CAD/CAM

Computer Software

Google Analytics

Customer Oriented

**HOBBIES** 

Music, Sports, Travel.

LANGUAGES

## Dental Technician, Hideg Dominic lab

Aug 2016 — Aug 2017, CLUJ-NAPOCA

- · Cad development
- Cad-Cam software technician

# Dental Technician, Dentina SRL

Aug 2015 — Aug 2016, Brasov

- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Cad- Cam technician

#### Dental Technician, Dentalmed

Aug 2014 — Aug 2015, Brasov

- Served as a positive and enthusiastic team player.
- Functioned with a high level of techical competency.
- Effectively managed projects from start to finish.

#### **COURSES**

## JavaScript Development/React JS, Scoala Informala de IT

Jul 2020 — Present

## Using a code editor, Laura Holmes Grasshopper Founder & CEO

Feb 2020 — Apr 2020

# Coding Fundamentals I & II , Laura Holmes Grasshopper Founder & CEO

Jan 2020 — Aug 2020

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Medicine and Pharmacy, Dental Technician

Aug 2010 — Aug 2013, Tg Mures

## College of Music, CANTO

Aug 2010 — Aug 2010, Brasov

English

Romanian